Front End Web Developer

RHONDA GOOLSBY

Phone: (919) 943-7503 | Email: rlgoolsby@gmail.com

Portfolio: http://rlgoolsby.github.io/Profile
Address: Carrboro, North Carolina

Objective

Prioritizing the user experience when bringing a design concept to life and building applications where all users have equal access to information. Working with a team that knows the importance of inclusiveness, good communication, and the value of creating user-friendly applications.

Skills

Languages

HTML5, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), JavaScript, Ruby

Tools

Git, Github, Agile Methodology, Microsoft Teams, Jira, Postman

Libraries, Frameworks, and CMS JQuery, Rails, AngularJS, Bootstrap, Magento, Shopify, IBM Management

Center

Relevant Experience

WEB AND TECHNICAL SUPPORT SPECIALIST - Trivantage LLC - Burlington, NC - Aug 2017 to Present

Support the digital presence of external and internal websites. This includes assisting customers and internal employees
while troubleshooting issues that may arise. Provide project management for all code revisions implemented for various
sites. QA test new code features and bug fixes. Revise and build code to enhance existing and new site functionality.

WEB CONSULTANT - GROW WELL NC - Chapel Hill, North Carolina - Jan 2017 - Feb 2017

 Provide volunteer website consultation services that includes code debugging and content replacement on a WordPress website.

WEB CONTENT MANAGER - Benevolence Farm - Graham, North Carolina - Sept 16 - Oct 16

 Provide volunteer website management services that includes revising style elements, debugging, and content replacement on a WordPress website.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER STUDENT - The Iron Yard - Durham, North Carolina - Feb 15 - Aug 16

- Completed a 24-week total immersion programming boot camp focused on Front End Engineering practices for building interactive web-applications.
- Completed weekly technical projects individually and within teams and over a six-month period to learn and gain knowledge around current development tools, techniques, and best practices.

Work History

CREATOR - DESIGNER - Green Sky Sustainable Design - Carrboro, North Carolina - Jan 08 - Dec 16

INSTRUCTOR - Chatham County Community College - Pittsboro, North Carolina - Jan 2009 - Dec 2010

COFFEE BUYER - Whole Foods Market - Chapel Hill, North Carolina -May 10 - Nov 14

HORTICULTURE SPECIALIST - Duke University - Durham, North Carolina - May 05 - Dec 07

Education

- . Front End Engineering Certificate, The Iron Yard, Durham, NC
- Coursework toward Masters of Education, GA State University, Atlanta. GA
- Bachelor of Science in Psychology, Berry College, Rome, GA